### Search

Search titles only

By: 

Search [Advanced search…](https://xiaomi.eu/community/search/)

Search titles only

By: 

Search [Advanced…](https://xiaomi.eu/community/search/)

### Search

Search titles only

By: 

Search [Advanced search…](https://xiaomi.eu/community/search/)

Search titles only

By: 

Search [Advanced…](https://xiaomi.eu/community/search/)

Menu

Install the app

Install

Privacy policy
==============

JavaScript is disabled. For a better experience, please enable JavaScript in your browser before proceeding.

You are using an out of date browser. It may not display this or other websites correctly.  
You should upgrade or use an [alternative browser](https://www.google.com/chrome/).

Help pages

Help
----

We are Unofficial Xiaomi European Community | MIUI ROM Since 2010 ("we", "our", "us"). We’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. If you have questions about your personal information please [contact us](https://xiaomi.eu/community/misc/contact).

What information we hold about you
----------------------------------

The type of data that we collect and process includes:

* Your name or username.
* Your email address.
* Your IP address.

Further data may be collected if you choose to share it, such as if you fill out fields on your profile.

We collect some or all of this information in the following cases:

* You register as a member on this site.
* You fill out our contact form.
* You browse this site. See "Cookie policy" below.
* You fill out fields on your profile.

How your personal information is used
-------------------------------------

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

* For the purposes of making you a registered member of our site, in order for you to contribute content to this site.
* We may use your email address to inform you of activity on our site.
* Your IP address is recorded when you perform certain actions on our site. Your IP address is never publicly visible.

Other ways we may use your personal information.
------------------------------------------------

In addition to notifying you of activity on our site which may be relevant to you, from time to time we may wish to communicate with all members any important information such as newsletters or announcements by email. You can opt-in to or opt-out of such emails in your profile.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you in the course of your interaction with our site. This information may include technical information about the browser or type of device you're using. This information will be used purely for the purposes of analytics and tracking the number of visitors to our site.

Keeping your data secure
------------------------

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect.

Advertising
-----------

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this site

Google's use of the advertising cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the internet. The Personal Data collected are Tracker, Usage Data, as stated in their [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

Users may opt out of the use of the advertising cookie for interest-based advertising in their [Cookie preferences](https://xiaomi.eu/community/misc/cookies) (or follow Cookies link at bottom of every page)

Alternatively you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](https://youradchoices.com/)

Cookie policy
-------------

Cookies are small text files which are set by us on your computer which allow us to provide certain functionality on our site, such as being able to log in, or remembering certain preferences.

We have a detailed cookie policy and more information about the cookies that we set on [this page](https://xiaomi.eu/community/help/cookies).

Rights
------

You have a right to access the personal data we hold about you or obtain a copy of it. To do so please [contact us](https://xiaomi.eu/community/misc/contact). If you believe that the information we hold for you is incomplete or inaccurate, you may [contact us](https://xiaomi.eu/community/misc/contact) to ask us to complete or correct that information.

You also have the right to request the erasure of your personal data. Please [contact us](https://xiaomi.eu/community/misc/contact) if you would like us to remove your personal data.

Acceptance of this policy
-------------------------

Continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of this policy. If you do not accept the policy then please do not use this site. When registering we will further request your explicit acceptance of the privacy policy.

Changes to this policy
----------------------

We may make changes to this policy at any time. You may be asked to review and re-accept the information in this policy if it changes in the future.

CAPTCHA privacy policy
----------------------

This site is protected by hCaptcha and its [privacy policy](https://hcaptcha.com/privacy) and [terms of service](https://hcaptcha.com/terms) apply.

### About us

* MIUI Dev and Xiaomi Europe were founded in October of 2010 with official conscent from Xiaomi founders in Beijing to provide MIUI ROM users a community for English MIUI Android ROM and Xiaomi products. Since 2010 our web site has officially worked with Xiaomi on a variety of projects for APP translations (MIUI, Mi Home products) and bug fixing forming a large part of the Official Xiaomi Global ROM experience thanks to the great team at xiaomi.eu and its community.

### Quick Navigation

### User Menu

### Follow us on Facebook

* 

* We value your privacy
    ---------------------
    
    We use essential [cookies](https://xiaomi.eu/community/help/cookies) to make this site work, and optional cookies to enhance your experience. Cookies are also used for ads personalisation

    * Essential cookies
    
    These cookies are required to enable core functionality such as security, network management, and accessibility. You may not reject these.
    
    * Optional cookies
    
    We deliver enhanced functionality for your browsing experience by setting these cookies. If you reject them, enhanced functionality will be unavailable.
    
    * Third-party cookies
    
    Cookies set by third parties may be required to power functionality in conjunction with various service providers for security, analytics, performance or advertising purposes.

    Save cookie preferences
